enasco.com 2017-06-12

# Nasco | Privacy Policy Statement

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") discloses what information is gathered about visitors to our websites collectively, the "Websites"), however accessed, and how that information is used. The Websites are owned or operated by Nasco Inc. (the "Company," "we" or "us"), and we use the personal information we receive from the Websites as described below. We do not sell your personal information.

By using the Websites, or sharing your information with us, you consent to and accept the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## Online Information Practices

We are committed to protecting your personal privacy as you visit our Websites. As a visitor to our site, you have the right to understand our privacy and security practices prior to providing us with personal information.

## Information We May Collect

We collect personal information such as your name, company or organization name, address, e-mail, and phone number when you place orders on the Website or create an account. On all pages that collect personal information, we specifically indicate what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service you have requested.

## Browsing

When you visit our Website, we gather information including page requests (URL requests), time of your visit, your IP address, operating system, web browser software, and any cookies which were set during a previous visit to our site. IP address information is not distributed to third parties. We use this information to improve your overall experience. We use cookies to help with navigation through our web pages; they are not used to gather any personal information about users.

## How We Use Your Information

The information you provide to us is primarily used to help us better serve you. We use the information you provide us along with your payment information to complete your requested transactions. We also use that information to deliver you or contact you about the requested products/services or information. We may also use your personal information to provide important information about products or services that you are using. Additionally, we may send you information about new products and services or upcoming events or other products and services that may be of relevant interest to you. If you do not want to receive such marketing communications from us in the future, please let us know by e-mailing or mailing us at the below respective addresses and telling us the name and addresses that you would like removed for those communications.

## Who We Share Your Information With

We limit the release of information and we require privacy protections in our business relationships. We do not sell customer information. We may share your personal information with our affiliated companies, when required by law, or with third parties that perform functions on our behalf. From time to time, we make our customer mailing list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting.

## COOKIES

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which is then stored on your system. A cookie is useful for having the browser remember specific information across several pages or between visits to a website. A cookie does not store personally identifiable information or any sensitive information. Also, our site does not read any information stored in cookies given to you from other websites, except in rare cases where the other website is a provider of information or functionality within our website and that cookie is necessary to make our website function correctly.

Our website makes use of cookies for the following purposes:

Website administration and personalization

Completing your request

Analysis of page and website information that does not identify specific individuals

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Browsers may also be set up to display a warning when a cookie is used. You may even disable your browser from accepting cookies. In order to provide you with the best possible experience while visiting our website, please enable cookies within your browser. Many parts of our site do not function properly if you disable cookies. In order to access this website, you need to have cookies turned on.

## LEAVING OUR WEBSITE AND/OR LINKING TO THIRD PARTIES

Because our website is secure, your browser will display a warning box to inform you if you are leaving a secured portion of the site. Please be assured that our website is secure and we strive to ensure that any information you send us is safe. When you leave this website and go to another linked site, we are not responsible for the content or availability of the linked site. Please be advised that we do not represent either the third party or you, if you enter into a transaction on the third party site. Further, the privacy and security policies of the linked site may differ from those practiced by us.

## CONTROL OVER AND ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

We enable you to have control over the accuracy of your personal information. You can delete or change your personal information with Nasco at any time by contacting us via a method described under "Contact Us" below.

## Do Not Track

Third parties may collect information about you across different web sites, including our website. We do not currently have the capability to respond to web browser do not track signals or other mechanisms that provide you with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of this information.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

**Mail:**  
Nasco, Inc.  
901 Janesville Avenue  
Fort Atkinson, WI 53538

**Email:**  

**Telephone:**  
920.563.2446

This Page was last modified on April 5, 2017.
